



Key skills

- Sales
- Data Entry
- Excel
- MS Office
- Customer Support



Personal Information

City

Noida

Country

INDIA



Languages

- HINDI
- ENGLISH



Social links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kshitizkumar-77928b185

KSHITIZ KUMAR

Customer Support Executive



3 Years 0 Month



(+91) 8433415974





Profile Summary

An accomplished professional with a solid background in Business Process Outsourcing I have 1 years of experience in specific roles. I am recognized for my expertise in dealing customers for their services and my ability to drive process optimization and efficiency.



Education

B.El.Ed, 2021

Mahatma Jyotiba Phule Rohilkhand University (MJPRU)

12th, 2017

Uttar Pradesh, Hindi

10th, 2014

CBSE, English



Work Experience

Jul 2023 - Feb 2024

Customer Support Executive

Tech Mahindra

We have to do correction in customer credit profile as per project norms and inform the customer via email.

Oct 2022 - Mar 2023

Customer Service Associate

Concentrix Daksh India Pvt Ltd

There is an project of insurance for abroad clients and in this we have to manage customer as well as service provider via call and give them information about their insurance as per the norms.

Aug 2020 - May 2022

Lead Sales Associate

Softles Web LLP

Softles is a full service branding and marketing firm that helps visionary companies emphasize their strengths and elevate their brands.